(Sheldon:)Come on, Short Round.
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Raj:)Come on, guys!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
(Howard:)Let's see you run
(Howard:)with a bag of urine
strapped to your leg.
(Wil:)He's got the movie! Get him!
(Sheldon:)Why is there never a pontoon
plane when you need one?
(Bernadette:)She's been in there
a long time.
(Amy:)Clearly, losing Truth or Dare
upset her.
(Amy:)Perhaps we should try
to take her mind off it
(Amy:)with another popular
slumber party activity.
(Bernadette:)Ooh, like what?
Well, the Internet suggests
(Amy:)that slumber party guests
often engage
(Amy:)in harmless experimentation
with lesbianism.
(Bernadette:)Where exactly on the Internet
have you been looking?
(Amy:)Penny?
Oh, hey, Amy.
(Penny:)Look, I'm sorry I got
so upset. I just...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(Penny:)What are you doing?
(Amy:)Don't worry. I'll
avoid the nether ye.
(Bernadette:)I might have gone
with eating raw cookie dough.